

Masuk Mia A Full stack Web developer

01720565018

E-mail: dev.masuk@gmail.com

Website: masukmia.com

ABOUT ME

This is Masuk Mia,A Full stack web developer & Wordpress Specialist. My nickname is Masud Rana. I am From Sylhet,Bangladesh. I have a experience of 4 years on Web developer and WordPress Specialist. I have been complete a lot of real world project. I have a completed lot of real life python data science Project. I have been working fiverr at 2018 and I also working Upwork & Freelancer. I have a lot of project on wordpress.

Expertise: HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,JavaScript, ES6, React,

Comfortable: Node Js, Express, Firebase, MongoDB,

LIVE PROJECT LINK

1.portfolio:masukmia.com

3.https://masudportfolio.netlify.app/

2.https://drabdullahsayed.com/

4.https://mmstore.netlify.app/home.html

5.https://appland-reactis.netlify.app/

CERTIFICATION

Wordpress specialist

Shekh Rasel It Academy Web developer 2020 to 2021

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

Redux, React-Hooks, Material Design.

Familiar: React native, ,Graphql,SQL, etc.

I have been finished after 6 month this training.

shek kamal It academy Digital Marketing 2020

Online program covered how to identify new sales prospects and build an inbound marketing strategy.

Computer science and engineering Bsc in Cse

WORK HISTORY

A Web Designer February 2019 to Present Fiverr & Upwork

A Web developer November 2018 to February 2019 Sylhet It Academy

A Wordpress Developer fiverr & freelancer April 2018 to present

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sylhet International University
Sylhet
Bachelor's in Science
Computer science and engineering
Major subject Machine Learning
2017 to 2021
Graduated at SIU

University of JC Sylhet ISC 2016 Graduated JC,Sylhet

Masuk Mia

shamimabad,sylhet

01720565018

E-mail: dev.masuk@gmail.com Website: masukmia.com

Dear Sir,

I have been really happy to see a job posting which is 100% fit for my skills. I have got your job Posting. According to your job description, I have come to know that you are searching for an expert A Full stack Web developer with the updated knowledge of strong experience. Now-a-days very few people can be found who knows about the Full stack developer Recently I have successfully completed findroom website. For more information will you please visit my work history. Success is my main aim. I gain success by hock or by crook. And I have a strong belief that I will be able to satisfy you in this project. Hope I will be hired.

I have enough experience in Mern Stack. I had been working with this for 2 years.

I am assuring you that I can do this job in a better and professional way.

I am always available on whatsapp,this is my contact number-01720565018. I will be available more than 50 hours per week and able to start your project as soon as possible according to you. Thank you for your consideration.

Best Regards Masuk Mia

Maryk

Masuk Mia Software Engineer Name:Masuk Mia e-mail:dev.masuk@gmail.com portfolio link: masukmia.com